asool-qtr.com 2015-03-21

# Our Privacy Policy | Asool Qtr

What information do we collect?

We   
collect information from you when you register on our site, place an   
order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a   
form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate,   
you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may,   
however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party   
vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART  
cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to   
your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use  
of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network   
privacy policy..

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

-To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

-To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

-To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

-To process transactions  
Your  
information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged,   
transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever,   
without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering   
the purchased product or service requested.

-To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

-To send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

How do we protect your information?

We  
implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your  
personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal   
information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied   
sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer   
(SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only   
accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems,   
and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a   
transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security   
numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

Do we use cookies?

Yes  
(Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers   
to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow)   
that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your   
browser and capture and remember certain information

We use   
cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart,  
understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of   
advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site   
interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in   
the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist  
us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers   
are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except   
to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you   
can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being   
sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser   
settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our   
services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders   
by contacting customer service.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We  
do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your   
personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third  
parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our   
business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this   
information confidential. We may also release your information when we   
believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site   
policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.   
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided  
to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Third party links

Occasionally,  
at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or   
services on our website. These third party sites have separate and   
independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or   
liability for the content and activities of these linked sites.   
Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome   
any feedback about these sites.

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We  
are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online   
Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone   
under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all   
directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Terms and Conditions

Please  
also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use,   
disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our   
website at /terms

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

This policy is powered by Free Privacy Policy and Rhino Support. Compare Rhino Support to Zen desk and save!

Be Sociable, Share!

  *
